[{"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "How will that play for the prosecution given that she's such a crucial witness?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, you know, she was an unusually difficult witness to evaluate because she was like a surly kid up there.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Well, it is and isn't, Piers, because you have to remember the only issue here really is self- defense.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And Jayne Weintraub, I mean, if you take that at face value and that is the truth, that's a pretty devastating indictment of what George Zimmerman did, isn't it?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I didn't hear you.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do you watch \"First 48\"?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "A show, the \"First 48,\" when a victim died, they call the number that the victim called before, and they have it.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "I'm sorry, the \"First 48\"?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I think it is interesting that young people often learn about the criminal justice system from television, as opposed to in school.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Is that significant?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I'm leaving today.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "I certainly wouldn't -- I don't know for sure.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "How much more time do you think that you need to finish your cross?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "No, and I have to say, you know, the candor and the honesty, I mean, I just love that moment.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "You know, it's not a pleasant experience, is it?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "That's the biggest question.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Or are they arresting him because the other guys already flipped and turned against him?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, if, in fact, it's the same gun that was used, we don't know because -- and by the way, the search warrants have been sealed, the records have been sealed, so we really don't know.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Now, Gloria, how significant could that be in all this?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "There is this culture, isn't it?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "I think there is a culture of guns among young people, and I think that's the issue.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Of NFL players of having a gun, empowering themselves with a weapon?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, what you did get was a decision that I think lays the groundwork for decisions all across the country to establish marriage equality in every one of the 50 states.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Are you frustrated, though, despite the success, that what we didn't get today from the Supreme Court was a decision on a homosexual's constitutional right to get married in America?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "My reaction - my reaction is the same as that, and I want to amplify what David said.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What is your reaction to what Cardinal Dolan said?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "I don't know that -- because it was very difficult to hear your full question.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "When do you see America, given the way and the speed this is moving, actually moving to what California has in totality?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "A tragedy?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I think if you want to reject the right of the Catholic bishop's collectively, not just Dolan, to actually stand up for their values and you want to say that's -- and you want to trivialize it, that's your right, but in fact, I do believe states are making arrangements.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "That's a tragedy for America?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I just want to say, as a Christian, if you're concerned about traditional marriage, Kim Kardashian has done more harm to traditional marriage than any gay person.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Is this a tragedy for America, Van?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Well, you know, part of the reason we want to have this show \"CROSSFIRE\" is because the show, which we haven't talked about that much, is going to be a half hour long and we're going to have one topic at a time so we can actually get deep into this stuff.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Van, any good?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, if you were a viewer and if you're a court watcher and you liked this afternoon, you're going to love tomorrow because it's going to be more of the same.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Martin, just procedurally what is likely to happen tomorrow?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Not a chance.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "And on a bigger picture, do you think we're going to see Zimmerman give evidence himself?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Well, criminal trials are really always about individual cases.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "And in terms of the bigger issues this case raises, race being a factor as many people feared or is it really coming down to a test of Florida's self-defense laws?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Well, I mean we rely on each other a lot.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "How do you collectively as a team deal with that?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "It is extraordinary.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "How does he deal with the particular pressure that he gets, because it's extraordinary?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Do you think that you're going to see more professional athlete now having the courage perhaps spurred on by American public -- to be more open about things like their sexuality?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm just a lucky guy.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Am I not trying hard enough?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Against us?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Oh, boy.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "To be a champion?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Well, you just have to play the game and luckily it went our way.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Just generally, how do you deal with that kind of game where you just about get away with it?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Will LeBron be with you next year?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130626pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "All right?", "qSentId": 608}]